Guide to the William Martin Religious Right research collection, 1975-2000 MS 537
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series IV: Evangelists, 1975-1990 and undated (Boxes 99-121)
  - Subseries A: Billy Graham (Boxes 99-109)
    - France 86 (Box 100)
    - Hoover Ableman Article (Box 100)
    - Schools of Evangelism (Box 100)
    - BGEA Press Releases (Box 100)
    - Presidents: Kennedy (Box 101)
    - Presidents: Johnson (Box 101)
    - Presidents: Nixon (Box 101)
    - Personality (Box 101)
    - Preaching (Box 101)
    - Press (Box 101)
    - Periodicals (Box 101)
    - Photos (Box 101)
    - Politics (Box 101)
    - Social Involvement (Box 101)
    - Race (Box 101)
    - Theology (Box 101)
    - China (Box 101)
    - USSR (Box 101)
    - Fundamentalists (B) (Box 102)
    - Interview Schedules (Box 102)
    - Organization: Direct Mail (Box 102)
    - Organization: Finances (Box 102)
    - Organization: Media (Box 102)
    - Organization: Samaritan's Purse (Box 102)
    - Oral Histories (Box 102)
    - Alexander Haraszti (Box 103)
    - Chief Organizer of Billy Graham (Box 103)
    - Trips to Eastern Europe (Box 103)
    - Billy Graham Clippings (Box 103)
    - Billy Graham Clippings continued (Box 104)
    - Cassette Tapes - William Martin Billy Graham Tapes (Box 104)
      - 9/20/86 - Opening service, Paris Crusade (Box 104)
      - Blair Carlson, crusade director. Mike Evans, local missionary. Paris, Cambrais and Strassbourg satellite services. (Box 104)
      - 12/17/86 -Ken Chafin, former Dean of BG Schools of Evangelism that accompanied BG crusades. Also, pastor of South Main Baptist Church Houston for many years. More than anyone else, responsible for getting me introduced to Billy Graham and encouraging me to write a biography (Box 104)
      - 5/2/87 - John Wesley White, BG sermon helper. PhD from Oxford. Columbia, SC (Box 104)
      - 2/25/87 - Calvin Thielman, Pastor, Montreat Presbyterian Church, longtime Graham friend. Montreat. (Box 104)
      - 2/26/87 - T.W. Wilson. BG's major domo for years. 2/26/87. Montreat. (2.5 tapes) (Box 104)
      - 3/28/87 - Robert and Lois Fern. Asheville. (Box 104)
      - 2/26/87 - John Akers. Graham close associate in Montreat. Intellectual. CT senior editor at times. Key in Eastern Europe trips. Montreat. (Box 104)
      - 7/17/86 - Billy Kim, Korea; Nelson Fanini, Brazil. Amsterdam. (Box 104)
      - Luis Palau sermon, Amsterdam 1986 (Box 104)
      - Closing service, Amsterdam 1986 (Box 104)
      - Jim Newton, Jim Douglas. British associates, writers. Amsterdam (Box 104)
      - Alred Yeo, Amsterdam/Carl McIntire and Edgar Bundy, lunch, Amsterdam. (Box 104)
      - Gilbert Kirby. BG London office head. (Box 104)
      - 2/10/87 - Carl F.H. Henry. Key Evangelical intellectual, first editor of Christianity Today. Telephone. (Box 104)
      - 5/2/87 - Johnny Cash, Columbia. Interview and service (Box 104)
      - 9/19/86 - Paris Dedication service. Thomas Duggan, Pastor, American Church in Paris. 9/18/86 (Box 104)
    - Abstracts (notes) from many interviews. (4) (Box 105)
    - Akers, John. BG close associate, key intellectual associate, major player in Eastern Europe trips (Box 105)
    - Barr, Dave (Box 105)
    - Barrows, Cliff. BG chorister, VP of BGEA, closest friend. 2/24/87 (Box 105)
    - Beavan, Jerry. 7/27/88 (2) (Box 105)
    - Beaven 8/2/88 (Box 105)
    - Bewes, Richard, Rector, All Souls, London. 10/1/86 (Box 105)
    - Bruce, David. Crusade staffer, later became BG constant assistant, similar to T.W. Wilson role. / / Bill Brown 7/24/87 (Box 105)
    - Brown, Bill. + crusade service 7/26/87 (Box 105)
    - Busby, Russ. 4/30/87 (Box 105)
    - Reid, Gavin. 4/30/87 (Box 105)
    - Notes on books (Box 105)
    - CNN: "Legends" documentary on BG (Box 105)
    - Cody, Bill. 11/23/87 (2) (Box 105)
    - Colson, Charles. 4/18/89. Houston (Box 105)
    - Graham, Morrow. Interview (by someone else, 1971) (Box 105)
    - Corts, John. 8/5/87 (Box 105)
    - Covington, Wint. BG teenage friend. 8/9/88 (Box 105)
    - McKeown, Roy. BG firnd. (?) 8/10/88 (Box 105)
    - Notes by Dale Martin (Box 105)
    - Dienert, Fred. 10/5/87 (2) (Box 105)
    - Denver Crusade services (Box 105)
    - Durston, Fred. BGEA staffer. 8/5/87 (Box 105)
    - Nelson, Victor. BGEA staff. 8/5/87 (Box 105)
    - Haldeman, H.R. 8/14/89 and Ehrlichman, John. 8/15/89 (Box 105)
    - Notes on Graham films (Box 105)
    - Fisher, Lee. Cared for Graham children for extended periods with BG and Ruth out of country, summers, etc. (Box 105)
    - Ford, Leighton and Jean (BG sister). 3/4/89 (Box 105)
    - Graham, Billy. March 1989 (4) (Box 105)
    - BG press conference and sermons (Box 105)
    - Ian Paisley anti-Graham sermon (Box 105)
    - BG in Taiwan (Box 105)
    - BG abstract notes (Box 105)
    - Hoke, Don. 3/6/89 (Box 105)
    - Hoke, Don (with Akers and Graham notes) 3/6/89 (Box 105)
    - BG on AIDS (also something from Jimmy Swaggart) (Box 105)
    - Graham, Melvin (Brother) 11/17/87 (2) (Box 105)
    - Graham, Ned (Box 105)
    - Gustafson, Roy. 6/27/88 (Box 105)
    - Hoke, Shea. Abstract from interviews (Box 105)
    - Holley, Henry. Veteran crusade organizer, mostly in foreign countries. 11/25/87 Mydske, Norm. (Box 105)
    - Huffman, John. BGCA Oral Histories (5) (Box 105)
    - Huston, Sterling. 5/2/87. Director of U.S. Crusades (Box 105)
    - William Martin Billy Graham tapes (Box 105)
    - Jackson, Mississippi Crusade. May 1975. First meeting with Graham and team, long before the idea of a biography. But this led to Texas Monthly article in 1979, which led to book, begun in 1986. 3 tapes, include interviews with various Graham people, including Charlie Riggs, who organized the counseling program for years, and Don Bailey, BG PR head at the time. (Box 105)
    - Observations of Co-Laborer corps, which processes decisions at the end of each crusade service. (Box 105)
    - Notes from Oral Histories at Billy Graham Center Archives, Wheaton. (2) (Box 105)
    - Notes from Alexander Haraszti interviews and oral histories. (Box 105)
    - Notes on Crusades from microfilm at Archives (Box 105)
    - Cassette Tapes - William Martin Billy Graham Interviews (Box 106)
      - 4/30/87 - Columbia, South Carolina- Millie Diener, wife of Fred Dienert, who oversaw Billy Graham broadcasting for decades. She organized prayer efforts for crusades. (Box 106)
      - 5/1/87 - Columbia, South Carolina - Ted Dienert, son of Fred and Millie, married to Ruth (Bunny) Graham. Divorced. Died before 50. (Box 106)
      - 5/1/87 - Columbia, South Carolina - Ralph Bell. African-American evangelist, specialized in prison ministry. (Box 106)
      - 5/1/87 - Columbia, South Carolina. Howard Jones. First black evangelist with BGEA. Tape bad. (Box 106)
      - 5/1/87 - Columbia, South Carolina. Grady Wilson, longtime friend and associate evangelist of Billy Graham. (Box 106)
      - 5/1/87 - Columbia, South Carolina. John Innes, organist. (Box 106)
      - 3/27/87 - Asheville. Bob Terrell. Researcher, writer (Box 106)
      - 2/24/87 - Greenville, South Carolina. Cliff Barrows. Longtime chorister. (Box 106)
      - 2/24/87 Barrows home. Johnny Lenning (Barrows' assistant, man of many tasks). (Box 106)
      - 3/28/87 - Asheville. Robert and Lois Ferm. Longtime associates, researchers, historians of BGEA. (Box 106)
      - 2/26-27/87 - Billy Graham, Montreat (5). (Box 106)
      - 3/26/87 - Billy Graham, Montreat (2). (Box 106)
      - 2/9/87 - Baltimore. Lane Adams, former associate (2). (Box 106)
      - 2/10/87 - Annandale, MD. Ed Plowman, Journalist with CT, BG org. (Box 106)
      - 4/30/87 - Columbia, South Carolina. Tedd Smith, pianist, music director for decades. (Box 106)
      - 10/22/86 - Wheaton. Oyvind Aadland, Norway. (Box 106)
      - 4/29/87 - George Hamilton IV. Performance at Columbia Crusade. Billy Graham to South Carolina Assembly, part of crusade service. (Box 106)
    - Billy Graham 1986 Washington DC Crusade. April/May 1986. (Box 106)
    - Team Meeting (Box 106)
    - Team Meeting (concl), reception (Box 106)
    - Usher, Counselor, Choir preparation/Opening service (Box 106)
    - Opening service. GHW Bush, Mayor Bradley (Box 106)
    - Hill, E.V., sermon at Billy Graham School of Evangelism (Box 106)
    - Reardon, Tex, Crusade director (Box 106)
    - Reardon (concl.)/Service, sermon on "Solomon" (Box 106)
    - Cutler, Elwyn, Director of DC Crusade (Box 106)
    - Barnes, Tom (Box 106)
    - Phillips, Tom. Key academic in BGEA organizer (Box 106)
    - White, John Wesley. Helped Billy Graham prepare sermons over the years. Oxford PhD (Box 106)
    - Service. Sermon on loneliness (Box 106)
    - White, John (Box 106)
    - Maddox, Bob (Jimmy Carter's liaison to clergy; former President of Americans United) (Box 106)
    - Maddox (concl.)/ Service #5 (Box 106)
    - Service viewed from TV sound truck (Box 106)
    - Haqq, Akbar. Former Muslim, evangelist to Muslim countries (Box 106)
    - Haqq, concl./Gibson, Ernest. Black minister/ co-chair of DC crusade (Box 106)
    - Mayor's prayer (Box 106)
    - Halverson, Richard. Chaplain of House of Representatives (Box 106)
    - Sermon at Youth Service (Box 106)
    - Evans, Colleen Townsend, Co-chair of DC crusade (Box 106)
    - Kerstan, Reinhold. German associate. (Box 106)
    - Riggs, Charlie. Longtime trainer of counselors (Box 106)
    - Busby, Russ. Billy Graham photographer for decades (Box 106)
    - Riggs, Charlie. Longtime trainer of counselors (Box 106)
    - Final service (2) (Box 106)
    - ICIE Radio Updates. 4 tapes. (Box 106)
    - 3/11/88 - Johnson, Jimmie, BG youthful evangelist friend. (Box 106)
    - Logan, Curtis (Box 106)
    - Melroy, Catherine Graham. BG sister. //Larry Ross (concl) (Box 106)
    - Melvin, Billy. President of Nat'l Assoc. of Evangelicals 12/7/89 (Box 106)
    - NOTES from BG microfilm archives (6 tapes) (Box 106)
    - Brian Mills, Harvey Thomas. British leaders. 6/16/87, London. (Box 106)
    - Morris, Carloss, Houston BGEA (and Rice) board member (Box 106)
    - Mydske, Norm. BG missionary to South America (Box 106)
    - Nelson, Victor. Veteran minister, letter writer at BGEA. 8/5/87 (Box 106)
    - Nelson, cont. (Box 106)
    - Williams, Ralph. BGEA, Minneapolis. 8/15/87 (Box 106)
    - Nixon-Graham Correspondence. 1955-1960 (Box 106)
    - Stephen Olford. 4/21/58 (2 tapes) (Box 106)
    - Notes from oral histories, BG Center Archives (BGCA) 3 tapes (Box 106)
    - Osei-Mensah, Gottfried, BGEA African associate evangelist (Box 106)
    - Wood, Bishop Maurice (recorded in Parliament Building, sitting in chair of Archbishop of York, 10/2/86). Also, clippings from BGEA England files. (Box 106)
    - Phillips, Wendell (Box 106)
    - Plowman, Ed and Adams, Lane. Notes from interviews (Box 106)
    - Johnston, Art (Box 106)
    - Ross, Larry. BGEA PR director (3 tapes) (Box 106)
    - 3 tapes of transcriptions of interviews (Box 106)
    - Reading notes (Box 106)
    - BG scrapbook notes (Box 106)
    - London BGEA scrapbooks, minutes, magazine (The Christian) (Box 106)
    - Shea, George Beverly. (2) 3/5/89 (Box 106)
    - Team Meeting (TASC) November 1987 (3 tapes). The Homestead. (Box 106)
    - Charles Templeton. BG friend from early Youth for Christ days. (2) 12/2/87 (Box 106)
    - Tchividijian, GiGi, BG eldest daughter 10/25/90 (Box 106)
    - "Voices of Lausanne" (Box 106)
    - Notes on "Mr. Texas" film (Box 106)
    - Thielman, Calvin. Pastor, Montreat Presbyterian Church, family friend, mentor to Franklin. 2/25/87 Montreat. (Box 106)
    - Vaus, Jim. Former gangster, converted at 1949 LA crusade. 3/4/88. Also, notes from NAE publications (Box 106)
    - Notes on news clips (Box 106)
    - Wagner, Peter C. Fuller missionary expert. (Box 106)
    - Williams, Bob. 2/28/90. Director, Mission World (Box 106)
    - Williams, Bob. 6/16/87. London. With Brian Mills. 6/16/87 (Box 106)
    - Wilson, George. CEO, BGEA, Minneapolis. 8/3/87 (Box 106)
    - Wilson, Grady, 3/14/87 Charlotte. BG childhood friend, Associate Evangelist. (Box 106)
    - Connally, John. Former Gov. of Texas. BG friend. 1/30/91 (Box 106)
    - Billy Graham Book Chapter drafts I- III (Box 107)
    - Billy Graham Book Chapter drafts IV - V (Box 108)
    - Billy Graham Book A Prophet with Honor draft (Box 109)
    - Billy Graham Research (Box 109)
  - Subseries B: Subseries B: Other Evangelists (Boxes 110-121)
    - A.A. Allen (Box 110)
    - Angley, Ernest (Box 110)
    - Arms, Phil (Box 110)
    - Armstrong, Herbert W. and Ted (Box 110)
    - Ambassador Report (Box 110)
    - Bishop, J.C. (Box 110)
    - Bryant, Anita (Box 110)
    - Burpo, C.W. (Box 110)
    - Carr, James Bishop (Box 110)
    - Carver, Kathy (Box 110)
    - Cerullo, Morris (Box 110)
    - Chosen People (Box 110)
    - Christian Jew Foundation (Box 110)
    - Coburn, Vic (Box 110)
    - Cooper, George W. (Box 110)
    - Copeland, Kenneth (Box 110)
    - Crews, Joe (Box 110)
    - Dehaan, Richard (Box 110)
    - Desmond, Perry (Box 110)
    - Douglas, John Sr. (Box 110)
    - Duncan, E.E. (Box 110)
    - Epley, David (Box 111)
    - Epp, Theodore (Box 111)
    - Estep, Howard (Box 111)
    - Roosevelt, Franklin (Box 111)
    - Frisby, Neal (Box 111)
    - Gage, Freddie (Box 111)
    - Gortner, Marjorie (Box 111)
    - Hagin, Kenneth (Box 111)
    - Harrington, Bob (Box 111)
    - Hargis, Billy James (Dr. Martin's note: see Patriots file) (Box 111)
    - Humbard, Rex (Box 111)
    - Hunter, Chas/Frances (Box 111)
    - Jenkins, Leroy (Box 111)
    - Jessup, J. Charles (Box 111)
    - Jones, Larry (Box 111)
    - Kuhlman, Kathryn (Box 111)
    - Kirban, Salem (Box 111)
    - Lord, Michael (Box 111)
    - Mann, Kenn (Box 111)
    - McGee, J. Vernon (Box 111)
    - McIntire, Carl (Dr. Martin's note: *see Patriots file) (Box 111)
    - McReynolds, A.B. (Box 112)
    - Osborne, T.L. (Box 112)
    - Panos, Chris (Box 112)
    - Reagan, David (Box 112)
    - Redmond, Charles (Box 112)
    - Relfe, Mary Stewart (Box 112)
    - Robertson, Pat (Box 112)
    - Roberts, Oral (Box 112)
    - Roloff, Lester (Box 112)
    - Schambach, R.W. (Box 112)
    - Schuller, Robert (Box 112)
    - Scott, Eugene (Box 112)
    - Smith, J. Harold (Box 112)
    - Sutton, Hilton (Box 112)
    - Terrell, David (Box 112)
    - Thrower, Bob (Box 112)
    - Tilton, Robert (Box 112)
    - Todd, Cecil (Box 112)
    - Trinity Broadcasting (Box 112)
    - Van Impe, Jack (Box 112)
    - James Dobson: Focus on Family (Box 113)
    - Pat Robertson: Christian Coalition (Box 113)
    - Pat Robertson: Christian Broadcasting Network (Box 113)
    - James Robison: Various Files (Box 113)
    - James Robison continued: The Evangelist (Box 114)
    - James Robison continued: Robison outlines (Box 114)
    - Jerry Falwell: Moral Majority (Box 114)
    - Jerry Falwell: Issues of Falwell Publications, June 1980-October 1987 (Box 114)
    - Jerry Falwell: Various Files (Box 114)
    - Leaders of Organizations: (Box 115)
      - Barton, David and Wallbuilders (Box 115)
      - Bright, Bill (Box 115)
      - CATO Institute (Box 115)
      - Campus Institutions (Box 115)
      - Christian Voice (Box 115)
      - Citizens for Excellence in Education (Box 115)
      - Colleges (Box 115)
      - Council on National Policy (Box 115)
      - Concerned Women for America (Box 115)
      - Family Research Council (Box 115)
      - Heritage Foundation (4f) (Box 115)
      - JSEA - organization (Box 115)
      - Evangelists, 1972-1984 (Box 115)
      - Bauer, Gary (Box 116)
      - Bauer, Gary Research Leads (Box 116)
      - Blackwell, Morton (Box 116)
      - Carter and Ford Presidential Archives (Box 116)
      - Campbell, Phillip (Box 116)
      - Christian Coalition (Box 116)
      - State Christian Coalitions (Box 116)
      - Christian Homeschooling (Box 116)
      - Conservative Foundations (Box 116)
      - Crusade Survey Summer (Box 116)
      - Cox, Harvey (Box 116)
      - Diamond, Sara (Box 116)
      - Family Issues (Box 116)
      - Farris, Mike (Box 116)
      - Graham, Franklin (Box 116)
      - Hart, Pat - Orlando (Box 116)
      - Horton, Michael (Box 116)
      - James, Kay Cole (Box 116)
      - Kilberg, Bobbie Greene (Box 116)
      - Horton, Michael (Box 116)
      - Miscellaneous Evangelists (Box 116)
      - Florida School Board (Box 116)
      - Lake County, Florida (Box 116)
      - Mary Cummins/Queens School Board Catholics (Box 116)
      - Unreviewed School Boards (Box 116)
      - Unreviewed School Boards (Box 116)
      - Research Leads on School Districts (Box 116)
      - Religious Right 1980 National Affairs Briefs (Box 116)
      - Swaggart, Jimmy Lee - Catholics (Box 116)
      - Swaggart, Jimmy Lee - The Evangelist (Box 116)
      - Swaggart, Jimmy Lee - Financial (Box 116)
      - Swaggart, Jimmy Lee - General (2f) (Box 116)
    - Summit Ministries (Box 117)
    - Walker, Jerry B. (Box 117)
    - Webber, David (2f) (Box 117)
    - Wheat, C.E. (Box 117)
    - Wyrich, Al (Box 117)
    - Miscellaneous Preachers including Graham, Falwell, Bakker, Robison, Robertson, Terrell, Swaggart, Jaggers, Roberts and Scandals (7f) (Box 117)
    - Televangelist Summaries 1981-82, 83 (2f) (Box 117)
    - Televangelist Summaries 1984, 85 (Box 117)
    - Televangelist Summaries 1986-87 (3f) (Box 117)
    - Televangelist Summaries 1988, 89 (2f) (Box 118)
    - Televangelist Summaries 1990-91, 92 (2f) (Box 118)
    - Televangelist Summaries 1993, 94, 95-96 (2f) (Box 118)
    - Dobson Radio Broadcasts (2f) (Box 118)
    - Dobson Tapes (Box 118)
    - Robertson Analysis 1983-86 (2f) (Box 118)
    - Robertson Analysis 1987-present (Box 118)
    - Robertson Analysis - Press releases, no dates, etc. (2f) (Box 118)
    - Robertson Campaign 9/24/86 - 8/7/85 (Box 118)
    - Robertson Campaign 9/11/87 - 9/24/86 (2f) (Box 119)
    - Robertson Campaign 12/3/87 - 9/11/87 (2f) (Box 119)
    - Robertson Campaign 4/10/95 - 1/3/88 (2f) (Box 119)
    - David Epley, Florida Healer. notes (Box 119)
    - Ernest L. Martin. Theologian, formerly part of Armstrong's Worldwide Church of God. Left the church before it disbanded. (3) Interview 6/28/75 (Box 119)
    - Brother Frank Tulloch (no idea as to who he was) (Box 119)
    - Paul Webb (2). Tapes in Los Angeles 8/29/75 (at the round Holiday Inn on the 405, where Santa Monica intersects the 405) Webb was a key figure in convincing UHF stations to air the programs of television evangelists, with Kathryn Kuhlman as his primary client. This was a godsend to UHF stations, many of which were failing. By running the programs, they did not have to sell advertising and had a dependable income. In the early days, before satellite TV and cable station, the stations would "bicycle" the tapes, playing them on their station, then sending them to the next station on the list. In that way, the evangelists had to make only a limited number of tapes. (Box 119)
    - Yeaworth, Irwin "Shorty" Pioneer in market research on TV evangelists. Also a filmmaker - worked on Billy Graham films. (Box 119)
    - Jones, Melvin (?) and David Webber, Oklahoma prophecy teacher with radio program (Box 119)
    - Rev. Al (A.L. Wyrich) radio show, and 1976 National Religious Broadcasters workshop on direct mail. (Box 119)
    - Charles and Frances Hunters' healing service Nov. 17, 1983 (Box 119)
    - David Wilkerson - Pentecostal preacher who pioneered dealing with drug addicts in NYC elsewhere. Played by Pat Boone in movie "Cross and Switchblade." Sermon from May 30, 1982. (Box 119)
    - Jimmy Swaggart Chapel Service (Box 119)
    - JS ability to run his organization (Box 119)
    - JS on Catholics (Box 119)
    - JS response to criticism (Box 119)
    - 1984 sermon on future of US (Box 119)
    - TV shows (Box 119)
    - Live Service in Houston Music Hall, 2/85 (Box 119)
    - Live Service Houston Coliseum (or Music Hall) 2/1985 "Secular Humanists" (Box 119)
    - Sermon tape 2/23/85 (Box 119)
    - William Martin Evangelist Tapes (Box 119)
    - W. Leo Daniels. African-American Houston evangelist (Box 119)
    - Robert Schuler on 60 Minutes. June 21, 1978 (Box 119)
    - Schuller. Dedication of Crystal Cathedral. 9/21/1980 (Box 119)
    - Ernest Angley TV show (Box 119)
    - Angley on Tom Snyder, Tomorrow. 8/24/79 (Box 119)
    - Marilyn Hickey, Interview. TV Bible teacher. Never big. (Box 119)
    - Richard Roberts (Oral's son) (Box 119)
    - James Robison, Oral Roberts, Jerry Falwell. (Programs?) (Box 119)
    - David Terrell - Wild man. Radio broadcast. / / Mack Watson. Houston radio preacher. (Box 119)
    - Ralph Wilkerson. Melodyland Christian Center. Anaheim, CA. Interview 8/28/75. (Box 119)
    - David Epley Service. 5/21/73 (Box 119)
    - CBN Telethon. January 1984. (Box 119)
    - William Martin Religious Right Tapes (Box 119)
    - Baylor Conference on Religion and Politics (5 tapes). (Box 119)
    - Jerry Falwell "I Love America" Rally. 1980 (2) (Box 119)
    - Falwell on "Sixty Minutes" and "Meet the Press" 1980, prior to election. Sept and Oct. (Box 119)
    - Donahue Show 12/10/80, shortly after Reagan elected: James Robison, Richard Viguerie, Terry Dolan (Box 119)
    - Televangelism radio interview, WTBS, with WCM (Box 120)
    - Rex Humbard and Ernest Angley TV programs (Box 120)
    - Pat Robertson interview 10/8/75 (cont.)/Ben Armstrong, head of National Religious Broadcasters, interview, 10/9/75 (Box 120)
    - Ben Armstrong (concl) (Box 120)
    - WCM on KSKY, Dallas. Other items (Box 120)
    - Dave Beaver (2 - not sure who he was/is) (Box 120)
    - Don Bogue (California) 2.5 tapes (Box 120)
    - Wendell St. Clair. 3.5 tapes. As a boy, was part of scene at Aimee Semple McPherson's Angelus Temple. Later, worked for Kathryn Kuhlman. Fascinating interview. (Box 120)
    - Kathy Carver. Abstract of interview. Traveling Pentecostal evangelist. Not on TV or radio to best of my knowledge. Appeared in Houston several times (Box 120)
    - Sven Blomberg. Interviewed by David E. Harrell for his book All Things Are Possible. Definitive history of the post-war healing revival. (Box 120)
    - J.C. Bishop, Dallas radio preacher. Interview 1/24/75 (Box 120)
    - C.W. Burpo, 3 tapes of his radio programs (Box 120)
    - NOTES from IRS documents (2) (Box 120)
    - Larry Jones, head of Feed the Children ministry from Oklahoma. (Box 120)
    - William Martin Evangelist Tapes (Box 120)
    - Billy James Hargis on Tom Snyder Show. 12/28/77, after scandal. Hargis was strong anit-Communist preacher with TV show (Christian Crusade) and American Christian College in Tulsa. He was ruined when a couple whose marriage he performed confessed on their wedding night that both had had sex with Hargis. Others were shown to have been involved. (I had this information before the scandal was revealed in TIME, but I didn't quite know what to do about it. I had planned to include it in a book, but was scooped.) (Box 120)
    - Hargis interview. After scandal 3/31/76 (3) (Box 120)
    - Bob Harrington, the Chaplain of Bourbon Street. Funny, popular preacher with ministry on Bourbon St. and on TV. Seemed to be on the rise, but was outed for sexual scandal and alcohol abuse. Lost his family and ministry. Once asked me if I would be interested in ghost-writing books for him I didn't (8 tapes, including an interview with Don Randon, his PR man, and notes.). (Box 120)
    - Chaplain Ray Hoekstra (2 tapes). Prison ministry. I can't remember who Sensig was. (Box 120)
    - C.B. Hollis, interviewed by David E. Harrell. (Box 120)
    - Johnnie Hope. Former Evangelist, worked with numerous ministries. Lived in Tulsa at the time of interview, 8/14/75. Wide knowledge of the industry. Later saw him at Billy Graham Amsterdam '86 event, where he was conducting a workshop. (5 tapes) Part of interview with Ken Lybarger, Two with Paul Locke. (Box 120)